Guide to the Sterling Lord Archive 1946-1998 MSS 058
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Financial, Administrative, and Legal
  - Subseries A: Administrative and Legal papers
    - "Sins" - New World TV - STER-490, 1985 (Box 275, Folder 30)
    - "The Six-Killer Chronicles" - STER-479, 1985 (Box 275, Folder 31)
    - "Slayride" - STER-306, 1974 (Box 275, Folder 32)
    - "Slide" - Yablans - STER-357, 1976 (Box 275, Folder 33)
    - "Smokescreen" - Levinson - STER-345, 1975 (Box 275, Folder 34)
    - "Son of Sam" - Lorimar - STER-399, 1978 (Box 275, Folder 35)
    - Souvenir Press, 1962 (Box 275, Folder 36)
    - Souvenir Press, 1962 (Box 275, Folder 37)
    - Souvenir Press, 1963 (Box 275, Folder 38)
    - Souvenir Press - Completed deals, 1962 (Box 276, Folder 1)
    - Souvenir Press - Completed deals, 1962-1963 (Box 276, Folder 2)
    - Souvenir Press - Euro-Features, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 3)
    - Souvenir Press - Payments, 1962 (Box 276, Folder 4)
    - "Space Fling" - STER-340, Undated (Box 276, Folder 5)
    - "The Spy Who Got Away" - STER-604, 1987 (Box 276, Folder 6)
    - Sterling Lord Adv. - Jess Stearn - STER-416, 1979-1983 (Box 276, Folder 7)
    - Sterling Lord - Agency Dissolution, 1984-1988 (Box 276, Folder 8)
    - Sterling Lord apartment - 31E. 72nd St. - STER-607, 1987 (Box 276, Folder 9)
    - Sterling Lord apartment - Crossland Mortgage - STER-607A, 1987 (Box 276, Folder 10)
    - Sterling Lord - Bookkeeping, 1989-1990 (Box 276, Folder 11)
    - Sterling Lord - Columbia Univ. Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 276, Folder 12)
    - Sterling Lord - Desk calendar, 1953 (Box 276, Folder 13)
    - Sterling Lord - Desk calendar, 1954 (Box 276, Folder 14)
    - Sterling Lord - Desk calendar, 1956 (Box 276, Folder 15)
    - Sterling Lord - Desk calendar, 1957 (Box 276, Folder 16)
    - Sterling Lord - Desk calendar, 1960 (Box 276, Folder 17)
    - Sterling Lord - Misc., 1955-1957 (Box 276, Folder 18)
    - Sterling Lord - Misc., 1958 (Box 276, Folder 19)
    - Sterling Lord - Misc., 1959 (Box 276, Folder 20)
    - Sterling Lord - Notes, 1958 (Box 276, Folder 21)
    - Sterling Lord - Office alterations, 1968-1977 (Box 276, Folder 22)
    - Sterling Lord - Office lease - STER-408, 1978 (Box 276, Folder 23)
    - Sterling Lord - Office lease - STER-408, 1978 (Box 276, Folder 24)
    - Sterling Lord - Office lease - STER-442, 1981 (Box 276, Folder 25)
    - Sterling Lord - Office lease - STER-448, 1982 (Box 277, Folder 1)
    - Sterling Lord - Office lease - STER-624, 1987 (Box 277, Folder 2)
    - Sterling Lord - Office papers and correspondence, 1968-1981 (Box 277, Folder 3)
    - Sterling Lord - Personal (1 of 2), 1993-1994 (Box 277, Folder 4)
    - Sterling Lord - Personal (2 of 2), 1993-1994 (Box 277, Folder 5)
    - Sterling Lord - Personal (1 of 2), 1994 (Box 277, Folder 6)
    - Sterling Lord - Personal (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 277, Folder 7)
    - Sterling Lord Agency - Name change cards, Undated (Box 277, Folder 8)
    - Steven J. Axelrod- STER-446, 1982-1983 (Box 277, Folder 9)
    - Steven Levy - STER-489 (Box 277, Folder 10)
    - "Sting Man" - STER-428, 1980 (Box 277, Folder 11)
    - "Stone 588" - Worldvision - STER-623, 1987 (Box 277, Folder 12)
    - Stuart Krichevshy contract - STER-515, 1986 (Box 277, Folder 13)
    - Sub-lease for 30W 61st St. - STER-496, 1985 (Box 277, Folder 14)
    - "Subway Stalker" - STER-529, 1986 (Box 277, Folder 15)
    - "Target Blue" - Universal TV - STER-538, 1986 (Box 277, Folder 16)
    - "Table Money" - STER-541, 1986 (Box 277, Folder 17)
    - "The Target is Destroyed" - STER-549, 1986 (Box 277, Folder 18)
    - "Texas Whore House" (1 of 4) - STER-404, 1978 (Box 277, Folder 19)
    - "Texas Whore House" (2 of 4) - STER-404, 1978 (Box 277, Folder 20)
    - "Texas Whore House" (3 of 4) - STER-404, 1978 (Box 277, Folder 21)
    - "Texas Whore House" (4 of 4) - STER-404, 1978 (Box 277, Folder 22)
    - Thomson and Morash - STER-467, 1984 (Box 277, Folder 23)
    - "Time and Again" - STER-320, 1975 (Box 277, Folder 24)
    - "Time Out" - STER-418, 1979 (Box 277, Folder 25)
    - "To Kill a Cop" - Columbia (1 of 2) - STER-385, 1977 (Box 277, Folder 26)
    - "To Kill a Cop" - Columbia (2 of 2) - STER-385, 1977 (Box 277, Folder 27)
    - "To Set the Record Straight" - Mendelson, Gallu - STER-423, 1979-1980 (Box 277, Folder 28)
    - Todd M. Harris - STER-482, 1985 (Box 277, Folder 29)
    - The Trial of Lee Harvey Oswald - STER-335, 1975-1977 (Box 277, Folder 30)
    - "Trial of Oswald" - Alpine - STER-351, 1975-1976 (Box 277, Folder 31)
    - "The Unicorn's Secret" - STER-620, 1987 (Box 277, Folder 32)
    - "Urban Cowboy" - Aaron Latham - STER-441, 1971-1981 (Box 277, Folder 33)
    - U.S. vs Criden - STER-431, 1980 (Box 277, Folder 34)
    - U.S. vs Hearst - STER-443, 1981 (Box 277, Folder 35)
    - Veronis, Suhler, and Associates - STER-465, 1984 (Box 277, Folder 36)
    - Vincent Bugliosi - STER-630, 1989 (Box 277, Folder 37)
    - Walton - "Free to Be" - STER-341, 1975-1976 (Box 277, Folder 38)
    - "Washington Wives" - STER-484, 1985 (Box 277, Folder 39)
    - Wayne Warga - STER-474, 1984 (Box 277, Folder 40)
    - "We Were Dreamers" - STER-352, 1975-1976 (Box 278, Folder 1)
    - Weed vs Rappaport - STER-324, 1975 (Box 278, Folder 2)
    - "The Western" - STER-313, 1974 (Box 278, Folder 3)
    - "The Western" - STER-453, 1982 (Box 278, Folder 4)
    - WGA - STER-425, 1980 (Box 278, Folder 5)
    - WGA-SAR - STER-455, 1983 (Box 278, Folder 6)
    - "Who Will Save the Children" - STER-539, 1986 (Box 278, Folder 7)
    - William Brinkley - STER-450, 1982 (Box 278, Folder 8)
    - "Wiseguy" - STER-525, 1986-1991 (Box 278, Folder 9)
    - "Wiseguy" - CBV - Jean Harris-MacMillan - STER-525C, 1987 (Box 278, Folder 10)
    - "Wiseguy" - CVB - Simon and Schuster - STER-525D, 1987 (Box 278, Folder 11)
    - "Wiseguy" - CVB - Statuses - STER-525B, 1987 (Box 278, Folder 12)
    - "Wiseguy" - CVCB (2 of 2)- STER-525A, 1986-1991 (Box 278, Folder 13)
    - "Wiseguy" - CVCB (2 of 2) - STER-525A, 1986-1991 (Box 278, Folder 14)
    - "Wiseguy" - Simon and Schuster (1 of 3), 1986-1991 (Box 278, Folder 15)
    - "Wiseguy" - Simon and Schuster (2 of 3), 1986-1991 (Box 278, Folder 16)
    - "Wiseguy" - Simon and Schuster (3 of 3), 1986-1991 (Box 278, Folder 17)
    - "The Woman He Loved" - STER-301, 1974 (Box 278, Folder 18)
    - "The Woman He Loved" - STER-625, 1987 (Box 278, Folder 19)
    - "World Without End, Amen" - STER-312, 1975 (Box 278, Folder 20)
    - "World Without End, Amen" - Columbia (1 of 2) - STER-406, 1978 (Box 278, Folder 21)
    - "World Without End, Amen" - Columbia (2 of 2) - STER-406, 1978 (Box 278, Folder 22)
    - "World Without End, Amen" - Gerber - STER-383, 1977 (Box 278, Folder 23)
    - "The World's Most Dangerous Job" - STER-610, 1987-1988 (Box 278, Folder 24)
    - "Young Mafia" - STER-517, 1986 (Box 278, Folder 25)
  - Subseries B: Financial papers
    - Agency Reports (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 279, Folder 1)
    - Agency Reports (2 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 279, Folder 2)
    - American Express, 1983 (Box 279, Folder 3)
    - American Express, 1983 (Box 279, Folder 4)
    - Annnual Financial Reports, 1952-1958 (Box 279, Folder 5)
    - Annual Financial Reports, 1959 (Box 279, Folder 6)
    - Annual Financial Reports, 1960 (Box 279, Folder 7)
    - Annual Financial Reports, 1961 (Box 279, Folder 8)
    - Annual Financial Reports, 1962 (Box 279, Folder 9)
    - Annual Financial Reports, 1963 (Box 279, Folder 10)
    - Annual Financial Reports, 1964 (Box 279, Folder 11)
    - Annual Financial Reports, 1965 (Box 279, Folder 12)
    - Annual Financial Reports, 1966 (Box 279, Folder 13)
    - Annual Financial Reports, 1967 (Box 279, Folder 14)
    - Annual Financial Reports, 1968 (Box 279, Folder 15)
    - Annual Financial Reports, 1969 (Box 279, Folder 16)
    - Annual Financial Reports, 1970 (Box 279, Folder 17)
    - Annual Financial Reports, 1971 (Box 279, Folder 18)
    - Annual Financial Reports, 1972 (Box 279, Folder 19)
    - Annual Financial Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 279, Folder 20)
    - Annual Financial Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 279, Folder 21)
    - Annual Financial Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 279, Folder 22)
    - Bank Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 279, Folder 23)
    - Bank Deposit Slips - Blue, 1959 (Box 279, Folder 24)
    - Bank Deposit Slips - Blue, 1959 (Box 279, Folder 25)
    - Bank Deposit Slips - Blue, 1960 (Box 279, Folder 26)
    - Bank Deposit Slips - Blue, 1960 (Box 279, Folder 27)
    - Bank Deposit Slips - Blue, 1960 (Box 279, Folder 28)
    - Bank Deposit Slips - Blue, 1961 (Box 279, Folder 29)
    - Bank Deposit Slips - Blue, 1961 (Box 280, Folder 1)
    - Bank Deposit Slips - Blue, 1961 (Box 280, Folder 2)
    - Bank Deposit Slips - Blue, 1961 (Box 280, Folder 3)
    - Bank Deposit Slips - Blue, 1962 (Box 280, Folder 4)
    - Bank Deposit Slips - Blue, 1962 (Box 280, Folder 5)
    - Bank Deposit Slips - Blue, 1962 (Box 280, Folder 6)
    - Bank Deposit Slips - Blue, 1962 (Box 280, Folder 7)
    - Bank Deposit Slips - Blue, 1962 (Box 280, Folder 8)
    - Bank Deposit Slips - Yellow, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 9)
    - Bank Deposit Slips - Yellow, 1960 (Box 280, Folder 10)
    - Bank Deposit Slips - Yellow, 1960 (Box 280, Folder 11)
    - Bank Deposit Slips - Yellow, 1961 (Box 280, Folder 12)
    - Bank Deposit Slips - Yellow, 1961 (Box 280, Folder 13)
    - Bank Deposit Slips - Yellow, 1961 (Box 280, Folder 14)
    - Bank Deposit Slips - Yellow, 1962 (Box 280, Folder 15)
    - Bank Deposit Slips - Yellow, 1962 (Box 280, Folder 16)
    - Bank Deposit Slips - Yellow, 1962 (Box 280, Folder 17)
    - Bank Deposit Slips - Yellow, 1962 (Box 280, Folder 18)
    - Bank of New York - Cash disbursements, 1982 (Box 280, Folder 19)
    - Bank of New York - Case disbursements, 1983 (Box 280, Folder 20)
    - Bank of New York - Cash receipts, 1979-1983 (Box 280, Folder 21)
    - Bank of New York - Reconciliations, 1982 (Box 280, Folder 22)
    - Bank of New York - Statements, 1983 (Box 280, Folder 23)
    - Bankers Trust Company, 1956-1958 (Box 280, Folder 24)
    - Bankers Trust Company - Reconciliation statements, 1961 (Box 280, Folder 25)
    - Bankers Trust Company - Reconciliation statements, 1962 (Box 281, Folder 1)
    - Bankers Trust Company - Statements, 1956 (Box 281, Folder 2)
    - Bankers Trust Company - Statements, 1957 (Box 281, Folder 3)
    - Bankers Trust Company - Statements, 1958 (Box 281, Folder 4)
    - Bankers Trust Company - Statements, 1959 (Box 281, Folder 5)
    - Berenstains - Royalty statements, 1963-1993 (Box 281, Folder 6)
    - Cash Reconciliation statements, 1960 (Box 281, Folder 7)
    - Castaldes, 1952-1957 (Box 281, Folder 8)
    - Check stub book, 1952-1953 (Box 281, Folder 9)
    - Check stub book, 1953 (Box 281, Folder 10)
    - Check stub book, 1954 (Box 281, Folder 11)
    - Check stub book, 1954 (Box 281, Folder 12)
    - Check stub book, 1954 (Box 281, Folder 13)
    - Check stub book, 1954-1955 (Box 281, Folder 14)
    - Check stub book, 1955 (Box 281, Folder 15)
    - Check stub book, 1955 (Box 281, Folder 16)
    - Check stub book, 1955-1956 (Box 281, Folder 17)
    - Check stub book, 1955-1956 (Box 281, Folder 18)
    - Check stub book, 1956 (Box 281, Folder 19)
    - Check stub book, 1956 (Box 281, Folder 20)
    - Check stub book, 1956 (Box 281, Folder 21)
    - Check stub book, 1956-1957 (Box 281, Folder 22)
    - Check stub book, 1956-1957 (Box 281, Folder 23)
    - Check stub book, 1957 (Box 282, Folder 1)
    - Check stub book, 1957 (Box 282, Folder 2)
    - Check stub book, 1957 (Box 282, Folder 3)
    - Check stub book, 1958 (Box 282, Folder 4)
    - Check stub book, 1958-1959 (Box 282, Folder 5)
    - Check stub book, 1977-1979 (Box 282, Folder 6)
    - Check stub book, 1977-1979 (Box 282, Folder 7)
    - Check stub book, 1979-1980 (Box 282, Folder 8)
    - Check stub book, 1979 (Box 282, Folder 9)
    - Check stub book, 1980-1981 (Box 282, Folder 10)
    - Check stub book, 1982-1983 (Box 282, Folder 11)
    - Client Analysis, 1986 (Box 282, Folder 12)
    - Coker Farm finances, 1981 (Box 282, Folder 13)
    - Coker Farm finances, 1982 (Box 282, Folder 14)
    - Commission Report (1 of 2), 1994 (Box 282, Folder 15)
    - Commission Reports (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 282, Folder 16)
    - Deposit Pass-Book, 1954 (Box 282, Folder 17)
    - Horse financial (1 of 3), 1982-1983 (Box 282, Folder 18)
    - Horse financial (2 of 3), 1982-1983 (Box 282, Folder 19)
    - Horse financial (3 of 3), 1982-1983 (Box 282, Folder 20)
    - Household taxes - back years (W2, W3), 1983 (Box 282, Folder 21)
    - IRS, 1981 (Box 282, Folder 22)
    - Legal services / fees, 1982 (Box 282, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous - letters owed, 1954 (Box 282, Folder 24)
    - Mixed bills and statements, 1983 (Box 283, Folder 1)
    - Mixed bills and statements, 1983 (Box 283, Folder 2)
    - Monthly Statements, 1968-1973 (Box 283, Folder 3)
    - Monthly Statements, 1974-1976 (Box 283, Folder 4)
    - Monthly Statements, 1977-1983 (Box 283, Folder 5)
    - Monthly Statements, 1981-1986 (Box 283, Folder 6)
    - Office - financial, Undated (Box 283, Folder 7)
    - Paid Bills, 1954-1957 (Box 283, Folder 8)
    - Paid Bills, 1954-1957 (Box 283, Folder 9)
    - Paid Bills, 1957-1959 (Box 283, Folder 10)
    - Paid Bills, 1957-1959 (Box 283, Folder 11)
    - Paid Bills, 1959-1960 (Box 283, Folder 12)
    - Paid Bills, 1959-1960 (Box 283, Folder 13)
    - Paid Bills, 1960 (Box 283, Folder 14)
    - Paid Bills, 1960 (Box 283, Folder 15)
    - Paid Bills, 1960 (Box 283, Folder 16)
    - Paid Bills, 1960 (Box 283, Folder 17)
    - Paid Bills, 1960 (Box 283, Folder 18)
    - Paid Bills, 1960 (Box 284, Folder 1)
    - Paid Bills, 1961 (Box 284, Folder 2)
    - Paid Bills, 1961 (Box 284, Folder 3)
    - Paid Bills, 1961 (Box 284, Folder 4)
    - Paid Bills, 1961 (Box 284, Folder 5)
    - Paid Bills, 1961 (Box 284, Folder 6)
    - Paid Bills, 1961 (Box 284, Folder 7)
    - Paid Bills, 1961 (Box 284, Folder 8)
    - Payment Receipt spreadsheets, 1989 (Box 284, Folder 9)
    - Payroll book, 1954 (Box 284, Folder 10)
    - Payroll book, 1955 (Box 284, Folder 11)
    - Payroll book, 1956 (Box 284, Folder 12)
    - Payroll records - FWT, FICA, IRS, 940, 941, 1980 (Box 284, Folder 13)
    - Payroll records - W2's, 1980 (Box 284, Folder 14)
    - Payroll records - W2's, P/R cards, 1980 (Box 284, Folder 15)
    - Pension Plan, 1985-1987 (Box 284, Folder 16)
    - Public National Bank and Trust Co. - statements, 1952-1953 (Box 284, Folder 17)
    - Public National Bank and Trust Co. - statements, 1954-1955 (Box 284, Folder 18)
    - Public National Bank and Trust Co. - statements, 1954-1956 (Box 284, Folder 19)
    - Publishing reports, 1961-1963 (Box 284, Folder 20)
    - Publishing reports - bank statements, 1961-1963 (Box 284, Folder 21)
    - Publishing reports - bills, receipts, 1961-1962 (Box 284, Folder 22)
    - Publishing report - log book, 1961 (Box 284, Folder 23)
    - Publishing report - subscribers paid, 1961-1962 (Box 284, Folder 24)
    - Rebecca Lord - Horse financials, 1982-1983 (Box 285, Folder 1)
    - Rebecca Lord - Horse financials, 1982-1983 (Box 285, Folder 2)
    - Receipts, 1954-1956 (Box 285, Folder 3)
    - Revenue reports, 1974-1988 (Box 285, Folder 4)
    - Revenue reports, 1985-1986 (Box 285, Folder 5)
    - SLA Canada - money due (1 of 2), 1994 (Box 285, Folder 6)
    - SLA Canada - money due (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 285, Folder 7)
    - Sterling Lord personal - bills, Undated (Box 285, Folder 8)
    - Sterling Lord personal - Chase Manhattan Bank statements, 1955-1958 (Box 285, Folder 9)
    - Sterling Lord personal - Corn Exchange Bank statements, 1949-1956 (Box 285, Folder 10)
    - Sterling Lord personal - expense stubs (1 of 2), Undated (Box 285, Folder 11)
    - Sterling Lord personal - expense stubs (2 of 2), Undated (Box 285, Folder 12)
    - Sterling Lord personal - Mixed financial documents, Undated (Box 285, Folder 13)
    - Sterling Lord personal - National Bank of Burlington statements, 1946-1950 (Box 285, Folder 14)
    - Sterling Lord personal - National City Bank of New York statements, 1952 (Box 285, Folder 15)
    - Sterling Lord personal - Payroll tax returns, 1976 (Box 285, Folder 16)
    - Sterling Lord personal - Public National Bank and Trust Co statements, 1954 (Box 285, Folder 17)
    - Tax documents - misc., 1983 (Box 285, Folder 18)
    - Tax information and forms, 1981 (Box 285, Folder 19)
    - Tax information and forms, 1978-1980 (Box 285, Folder 20)
    - Taxes - Agency, 1969-1981 (Box 285, Folder 21)
    - Taxes - Agency, 1981-1982 (Box 285, Folder 22)
    - Taxes - Agency, 1982-1988 (Box 285, Folder 23)
    - Weekly time book, 1958 (Box 285, Folder 24)
    - Cancelled checks - Bankers Trust Co., 1954-1958 (Box 286)
    - Cancelled checks - Bankers Trust Co., 1959-1960 (Box 287)
    - Cancelled checks - Bankers Trust Co., 1961-1962 (Box 288)
    - Cancelled checks - Public National Bank and Trust Co. (checks and deposit slips), 1952-1956 (Box 289)
    - Cancelled checks - Sterling Lord personal; Clients; Special account; Sterling Lord metal seal, 1946-1987 (Box 290)
    - [Flat Box] Berenstains - Royalty reports, 1972-1982 (Box 291)
    - [Flat Box] Berenstains - Royalty reports, 1983-1993 (Box 292)
    - [Flat Box] Berenstains - Royalty reports, 1994-1996 (Box 293)
    - [Flat Box] Berenstains - Royalty reports, 1996-1998 (Box 294)
    - [Flat Box] Bound check books, 1958-1959 (Box 295)
    - [Flat Box] Bound ledger book, 1955-1956 (Box 296)
    - [Flat Box] Cash books, Check stub books, Client ledgers, 1956-1959 (Box 297)
    - [Flat Box] Client ledgers, Commission reports, Deposit sheets, 1952-1990 (Box 298)
- Series III: Media
  Conditions Governing Access
  Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  This series contains the media that was removed from the paper files of this collection.
  - Subseries A: Audiocassettes
    - Juster, Norton - "The Phantom Tollbooth" - Attn.Todd Harris, 1986 (Box 299, Cassette ID: 058.0001)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      Format: Audiocassette
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Walk into my Voice: American Beat Poetry", 1995 (Box 299, Cassette ID: 058.0002)
    - Minor, Emily - "Two Pieces" 10-12-98, 1998 (Box 299, Cassette ID: 058.0003)
    - Summers, Anthony - "Putnam", 1990 (Box 299, Cassette ID: 058.0004)
  - Subseries B: VHS
    - Cowan, Warren - "TV Highlights of Kelly Lange and her novel, 'Trophy Wife'", 1995 (Box 299, Cassette ID: 058.0005)
      Format: VHS
    - Montardon, Pat - "Kremlin Meeting", 1987 (Box 299, Cassette ID: 058.0006)
  - Subseries C: CD
    - Sampas, Jim - "Waiting for the Fall" (two copies), 1994 (Box 299, Disk ID: 058.0007)
      General note
      This CD is a commercial release.
      Format: CD
  - Subseries D: Paper removed from media
    - Minor, Emily - "Two Pieces", 1998 (Box 299, Folder ID: 058.0003)
    - Summers, Anthony - "Putnam", 1990 (Box 299, Folder ID: 058.0004)
    - Cowan, Warren - "TV Highlights...", 1995 (Box 299, Folder ID: 058.0005)
    - Montardon, Pat - "Kremlin Meeting", 1995 (Box 299, Folder ID: 058.0006)
    - Sampas, Jim - "Waiting for the Fall", 1994 (Box 299, Folder ID: 058.0007)
- Oversize Series I: Subject Files
  This series contains the oversize material removed from Series I, Subseries B: Compiled Author / Publisher files.
  - Subseries B: Compiled Author / Publisher Files
    - Berenstains - Galleys, 1990-1994 (Box 300, Folder 1)
    - Nesbit correspondence - Photos of Tom Wolfe, 1965 (Box 300, Folder 2)
    - Newfeld, Jack - The Village Voice - April, May, 1965 (Box 300, Folder 3)
    - Newfeld, Jack - The Village Voice - June, August, September, October, 1965 (Box 300, Folder 4)